Most advanced, even fluent English students have had a shocking experience when they try to have a conversation in English.
即使是最先进、最流利的英语学生，在尝试用英语进行对话时也会有令人震惊的经历。
They don't speak with confidence.
他们说话时没有信心。
The sounds of American English are hard, and many people have never learned the correct pronunciation of each specific sound.
美式英语的发音很难，许多人从未学过每个特定音的正确发音。
Welcome to your Sounds of American English course.
欢迎来到您的美式英语发音课程。
In this course, you'll learn exactly how to make each sound in American English by studying how to move your tongue, lips, and jaw through illustrations and close-ups of the mouth.
在本课程中，您将通过研究如何通过插图和嘴部特写来移动舌头、嘴唇和下巴，准确学习如何发出美式英语的每个音。
You'll even learn the phonetic symbols for each sound, which is so important with English, since it's not a phonetic language.
您甚至会学习每个音的音标，这在英语中非常重要，因为英语不是一种拼音语言。
Letters don't always match with the sounds you would expect to hear.
字母并不总是与您期望听到的声音相匹配。
What?
什么？
This is colonel?
这是上校？
Where's the R?
R在哪里？
How comfortable are you making the TH?
您发TH音时有多舒服？
What about the American R?
美式R呢？
Don't let your spoken English skills get in the way of confidently meeting and speaking with others in English.
不要让您的英语口语技能妨碍您自信地与他人用英语交流。
The limits of my language mean the limits of my world.
我语言的局限意味着我世界的局限。
What are your limits?
您的局限是什么？
Leave them behind as you build a solid foundation for spoken English by perfecting the building blocks, the sounds of American English.
在您通过完善美式英语的基础音来建立坚实的英语口语基础时，将它们抛在脑后。
You can do this.
您可以做到的。